Eli Frenkin

054-535-6112 Holon e21211995@gmail.com

<u>Linkedin Profile</u>

Profile:

A self-motivated, and fast-learner Full Stack developer. I am a team player with experience developing websites using JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SASS, React, and SQL, a Cryptocurrency application using Redux Toolkit, and Ant Design which is fetching data using RapidAPI, and more. I look to my next challenge and believe I will significantly impact via my programming knowledge, my desire to develop my capabilities, my analytical thinking and keen attention to detail, and my communication and interpersonal skills.

Experience:

2021 - Today - Full Stack Developer - Freelancer

- Performing Full Stack development projects as a freelancer
- Developing applications and websites with various tools, such as JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SASS, React, SQL, RapidAPI, Python, and more

2017 - 2021 - Collection Manager - Diplomat

Diplomat is a leading sales and distribution company in Israel.

- Trained new employees and conducted quality assurance
- Managed projects to improve the working methods and warehouse's organization
- Performed products collection according to customers' orders
- Completion of inventory from the warehouse to the picking areas

Military Service:

2014 - 2017 - Combat Driver, Samaria Division

Education:

2021 - 2022 - Web App Development, IITC College

Tools & Programming:

Office environment, Redux, JavaScript, SQL, MongoDB, React, Express, RapidAPI, Bootstrap, FireBase, Python, Object oriented

Languages:

Hebrew - Mother-tongue

English - Fluent